A story of love
Gracie's Choice is a tv movie, drama film directed by Peter Werner.
For as long as she can remember, 16 year-old Gracie has been raising her four siblings, each of whom has
a different, absent father and their mother is on the fast track to self-destruction.
When these children's lives are about to be pulled apart, Gracie will have to do the
impossible and make the ultimate sacrifices to keep her family together.
Gracie Thompson, played by Kristen Bell.
Louela Lawson, played by Diane Ladd.
Tommy, played by Shedrack Anderson III.
Rowena Lawson, played by Anne Heche.
Judge, played by Roberta Maxwell.
Rose Carlton, played by Kristin Fairlie.
Gracie's Choice: A Story of Love is a 2004 American drama film
that premiered on Lifetime on January 12, 2004.
It is written by Joyce Eliason; directed by Peter Werner; and stars
Kristen Bell, Anne Heche, Diane Ladd, and Kristin Fairlie.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, judge,
adoption, custody battle, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.